Guide to the Historic Ephemera Collection 1880-2016
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Places (also see Travel)
  - North America
    - United States
      - Washington State
        - Seattle
          - Seattle Magazine. Hotel and Visitor's Guide. 1953 July.
          - The Seattle Greeter. Hotel and Motel Guide to Seattle. Transportation Issue. 1960 April.
          - "Constitution and Declaration of Principles of the Civic Union of the City of Seattle." Flyer.
          - Seattle: In the Charmed Land. Seattle Chamber of Commerce pamphlet. Circa 1930s.
          - "Vance Hotel, Seattle, Washington." Highway map of the State of Washington.
          - Pacific Northwest on Parade. 1937.
          - "Your Ticket to a Vacation Wonderland, in Seattle." Brochure. Seattle Chamber of Commerce. 1941.
          - Seeing Seattle by Water: Anderson Water Tours. Brochure.
          - "The Cobb Building: Office Tenancy Restricted Exclusively to Physicians and Dentists." Pamphlet. 1926.
          - Exhibitors' Bulletin, Pacific Northwest Merchants' Exposition. Seattle Chamber of Commerce. 1925 August.
          - "Americanus." Pageant Drama. University of Washington, Seattle. 1923 July 23-28. (Location note: in Oversize 1)
          - "American Youth for Murder." Flyer. Seattle, WA. (Location note: in Oversize 1)
          - "Student Anti-War Strike." Flyer. Seattle. (Location note: in Oversize 1)
          - Look at Life in Seattle. Seattle Chamber of Commerce. 1938. (Location note: in Oversize 1)
          - "An Evening in China." Invitation. China Club of Seattle. 1949.
          - Annual Report. Seattle Art Museum. 1943.
        - Sequim
          - "May Day Celebration." Official Program. Sequim Commercial Club. 1929 May 24-26.
          - "Sequim and Eastern Clallam County." Brochure. Sequim Commercial Club. Accompanying map.
        - Snohomish County
          - "Your Vacation in Snohomish County, Washington." Brochure. Chamber of Commerce. Everett, WA.
          - "Snohomish County on Puget Sound, Washington." Pamphlet. Circa 1930s.
        - Spokane
          - Camp Sweyolakan, 1926. Pamphlet. Spokane Council of The Camp Fire Girls.
          - Spokane: 1970 Automobile Route Guide and Directory of Grocers and Druggists. Pamphlet. The Spokesman-Review and Spokane Daily Chronicle.
          - A Farm Home for You. Farm Development Bureau of the Chamber of Commerce. Spokane, WA. Circa 1910s. (Location note: in Oversize 2)
          - Little Journeys. Pamphlets. Spokane Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1930s.
          - Little Journeys: Eighteen Loop Trips Throughout the Inland Empire. Spokane Chamber of Commerce. (Location note: in Oversize 1)
          - Interstate Coach Company coupon book. Spokane-Lewiston. Circa 1920s.
          - Spokane Valley bus time tables. 1938 October 3.
          - Inland Automobile Association directory. Brochure. Circa 1936.
          - Pamphlet for new headquarters building, Spokane and Eastern Division, Seattle-First National Bank. 1952.
          - Your 1948 Guide: Spokane Vacationland. Spokane Chamber of Commerce pamphlet.
          - The Dedication of the Spokane Plains Battlefield Monument. Program. 1926 July 23.
          - "City Map and Recreational Guide." Spokane. Circa 1940s-1950s.
          - "Dedication of Lincoln Memorial." Program. Circa 1930s.
          - Life in Spokane. Community Chest annual campaign pamphlet. 1939.
          - Spokane Falls Typographical Union No. 193. Job scale and apprentice regulations. 1917, 1918. (3 items)
          - The New Davenport Kitchen (The Proof of the Pudding is Not Always in the Eating). Pamphlet. Davenport's.
          - Spokane and the Intermountain Playgrounds. Brochure. Spokane Chamber of Commerce. 1936.
          - Spokane and the Intermountain Playgrounds. Lakes Brochure. Spokane Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1930s.
          - Forty Journeys into the Green Summer Playground Around Spokane. Pamphlet.
          - City of Spokane: Civil Service Rules. 1911.
          - Commentation for Spokane and its Inland Empire. Pamphlet (to accompany the motion picture "Spokane and Its Inland Empire"). The Spokesman-Review.
          - Miss Spokane Invites You. Brochure. Circa 1910s.
          - "Spokane, Northern Idaho and Montana." Hotel Greeters Tourist Guide. Pamphlet. 1941.
          - "Spokane." Brochure. Spokane Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1930s.
          - Important Facts Concerning Spokane, Washington and the Inland Empire. Brochure. Spokane Chamber of Commerce. 1955.
          - Spokane's Beauty Spots, reached by the Washington Water Power Co's city and interurban electric lines. Brochure. Circa 1915-1920s.
          - Come to the Land of Many Lakes: Spokane and the Inland Empire of the Pacific Northwest. Pamphlet. Spokane and Inland Empire, Inc. Circa 1910s-1925.
          - "Banking From Five Acres." Pamphlet. Greenacres Irrigated Land. Spokane Valley Land and Water, Co. Circa 1904.
          - Facts: Spokane: Metropolis of the Inland Empire and its Wonderful Progress in 1907. Leaflet.
          - Wooden nickels from Spokane, Washington's Golden Jubilee Celebration. (2 items)
          - One Sales Tax Emergency Token, Redeemable until June 1, 1935. Spokane Retail Trade Bureau.
          - Eastern Washington Historical Primer. Eastern Washington State Historical Society. 1943.
          - The Dilemma Facing Humanity. International Symposium I. Spokane, WA: Battelle. 1974 May.
          - Environmental Accomplishments to Date: A Reason for Hope. International Symposium II. Spokane, WA: Battelle. 1974 July.
          - Spokane Soroptimist. Vol. 2, No. 3. Spokane, WA. March 23, 1928. (Location note: in Oversize 1)
          - Dr. Chas. E. North. Veterinary Surgeon and Dentist. Business card. Spokane. Circa 1900s.
          - "Let's Celebrate the Golden Jubilee: Meet Us in Spokane." Poster. Circa 1939.
          - Spokesman Review order form and information. Circa 1925.
          - "Woman's Home Companion." Advertisement and order form. Circa 1925.
        - Steilacoom
          - "Steilacoom Centennial Celebration." Official program. 1952, 1953, 1954.
        - Sumner
          - "Sumner, Pierce County." Brochure. Sumner Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1950s.
        - Sunnyside
          - "1st Annual Ben Snipes Days." Souvenir Program. Sunnyside, Washington. 1958 June.
          - "Seventh Annual Sunnyside Pioneer Picnic and Monument Dedication." Souvenir Program. 1958 June 21.
          - Sunnyside at 60. Roscoe Sheller. Pamphlet. Inscribed to George A. Frykman by the author. Circa 1962.
        - Tacoma
          - Tacoma Invites You. Souvenir of Cushman Power Project. 1926.
          - "Christening of Towers and Official Opening of Cushman Power Project." Tacoma, WA. 1926 May 24.
          - The Port of Tacoma. Pamphlet. (Location note: in Oversize 1)
        - Tenino
          - Certificate Redeemable for 25 cents, printed on wood. Chamber of Commerce, Tenino, WA. 1932.
        - Tri-Cities
          - "Kennewick-Richland-Pasco: Columbia Park." Brochure. 1962.
        - Vancouver
          - "Recreation For You And Your Family!" Brochure. Vancouver Housing Authority.
          - "You Can Really Live in Vancouver, Washington." Brochure.
          - "Stay Another Day in Vancouver, Washington." Brochure. Vancouver Chamber of Commerce. (2 copies)
          - Fruit Valley Homes Tenant Handbook. Vancouver Housing Authority. Circa 1942-1945.
          - "Ogden Meadows Apartments." Vancouver Housing. Circa 1942-1945.
          - "Facts About Vancouver, Washington." Brochure. Vancouver Public Schools. Circa 1960.
          - Furs to Factories: The Story of Vancouver, Washington. Pamphlet. Vancouver Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1957.
        - Walla Walla
          - "Historical Walla Walla, cradle of Pacific Northwest History." Brochure. Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1950s.
          - "Walla Walla: Cradle of Pacific Northwest History." Brochure. Whitman National Monument Park. Walla Walla, WA.
          - "Walla Walla With Its Modern Marcus Whitman Hotel." Leaflet.
          - "Walla Walla in Wonderful Washington State." Brochure. Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1950s.
          - "Walla Walla, 1856-1952: Historical Landmarks." Leaflet. Circa 1950s.
          - "Walla Walla: the Home City in a Scenic Valley of Productivity." Brochure. Walla Walla Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1926-1930.
          - "Walla Walla." Brochure. Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1940.
          - "Whitman Centennial Celebration." Official Program. 1936 August 13-16.
        - Wenatchee and Wenatchee Valley
          - "Meadow Creek Lodge." Brochure. Wenatchee Chamber of Commerce.
          - "Visit Ohme Gardens." Flyer. Wenatchee, WA.
          - "What to See In and Near Wenatchee, Washington." Brochure. Wenatchee Chamber of Commerce. Circa 1948.
          - Welcome! To Wenatchee, Washington. Folder including brochures for Aplets and Cotlets and "Wenatchee Wonderland." Circa 1960s.
          - Nez Perce Indian Portraits. Rowena L. Alcorn. Exhibit catalog. Historical Museum Powerhouse Rocky Reach Hydroelectric Project. Circa 1970s.
        - Whitman County
          - "Metsker's Sportsmen's Guide: Whitman County Map."
          - "Metsker's Whitman County Map."
          - "Klemgard County Park: Self guiding Trail." Brochure. Whitman County Park and Recreation Department. Circa 1970s.
          - "The Palouse Country: the Home of Dry Edible Peas." Souvenir leaflet. Spokane, WA. 1951 August.
          - "Facts about Pullman, Washington and Whitman County." Brochure. 1970.
          - "A Few Facts About The Garfield Community, Whitman County, Washington." Pamphlet.
          - "Whitman County in Washington State." Pamphlet. Whitman County Commissioners. Circa 1973.
          - Know Your County--Whitman. Pamphlet. League of Women Voters. Pullman, WA. Circa 1958.
          - Soils Section. Technical Guide (mimeographed typescript). Work Unit Personnel of Whitman County. 1956.
          - Palouse Harvest Fair programs. October 5-7, 1916.
          - Family Theater program. April-May, 1940. Oaksdale, WA.
          - What to Do. H. C. Eitel. Booklet. Elberton, WA. Circa 1910s-1920s.
          - Whitman Mission. US Department of the Interior. National Park Service. 1972.
        - Yakima and Yakima Valley
          - "Fort Simcoe." Brochure. Yakima, WA. 1953.
          - "Yakima." Yakima Commercial Club brochure. Circa 1920s.
          - "Scenic...Historic...Yakima, Gateway to Mount Rainier National Park." Yakima Chamber of Commerce brochure. Circa 1940.
          - "Facts About Yakima, Washington and the Yakima Valley." Yakima Chamber of Commerce. Yakima, WA. 1964 August. 2 copies.
          - "Yakima Valley, Washington." Yakima Valley Chambers of Commerce brochure. Circa 1940s.
          - "Facts About Yakima, Washington and the Yakima Valley." Yakima Chamber of Commerce brochure. 1962.
          - "Yakima Hotel Motel Restaurant Guide." Brochure. Yakima Visitors and Convention Bureau.
          - "Hey! Lookee Here: Yakima..." Brochure. Yakima Chamber of Commerce.
          - A Review of Health Conditions and Needs in Yakima, Washington. Metropolitan Life Insurance Company. 1930.
          - Information Concerning the Kittitas Division of the Yakima Project, Washington. Elwood Mead. U.S. Government Printing Office. 1929.
          - "Yakima Invites You." Brochure. Circa 1950s.
  - Unsorted Items
- Politics and Government
  - Soviet Union/Russia
    - The Crimes of the Stalin Era. Nikita S. Khrushchev. New York: The New Leader. 1956.
  - United States
    - "Are You For La Follette? Then Vote For Knute Hill for Congress." Leaflet.
    - Humanist World Digest. Berkeley, CA. Vol. 25, No. 4. 1953 November.
    - "House of Representatives Restaurant U.S. Capitol." Menu. 1954 February 22.
    - "Anti-God Humanists Are 'Conditioning' Our Children." Phoebe Courtney. The Independent American. 1980.
    - The Case of the Blighted City. Edward C. Banfield. Chicago: American Foundation for Continuing Education. 1959.
    - "How 27 Men Can Capture the United States." Pacific Northwest Development Association. Brochure. Circa 1950.
    - "Diagram of the United States Senate." Leaflet. Circa 1937. (Note: 57th Congress, 1901-1903, but printed in 1937)
    - The Chicano. Collection of printed informational handouts. Circa 1968-1970s.
    - Republican National Financing Committee mailing. 1972.
    - 53rd Presidential Inaugural (for President Clinton) packet with invitation and inauguration information. 1993.
    - Negroes for a Constitutional Republican Victory mailing. 1972.
    - Invitation to Inauguration of John F. Kennedy. 1961.
    - Third Annual Congress of League of Pacific Northwest Municipalities. Seattle Rotary Club. Seattle. 1914.
    - Ku Klux Klan (also see Cage 4690)
      - Petition to join the Knights of the Ku Klux Klan (blank form).
      - "Forrest Announces Plans for University of America: Big Non-Sectional Institution to be Ready by Fall" (newspaper article--reproduction). The Constitution. Atlanta, Georgia. Sunday, 1922 February 5. Page 7. (Location note: in Oversize case)
      - Reproduced letter about Compulsory Educational Bill in Washington and Idaho, from Orvin R. Smith, Spokane, WA.
    - Washington State
      - "The Bone-Erickson 'Bill." Pamphlet. Northwest Electric Light and Power Association. 1924.
      - "Governor Martin means Stability and Progress for all of Washington." Leaflet. 1940.
      - "Initiative 171 Unmasked." Leaflet. Washington Temperance Association. Concerns nullifying law requiring liquor stores to be 500 feet from churches and schools. Circa 1940s-1950s.
      - "What is Initiative No. 13?" Leaflet. Washington Temperance Association. Concerns restriction of liquor sales (Initiatives 13 and 171). Circa 1940s-1950s.
      - Campaign flyer for Mon C. Wallgren as U.S. Senator, circa 1940.
      - "Lincoln Club of Washington." Leaflet. Everett, WA. Circa 1930s.
      - The Washington Taxpayer. Vol. 1, No. 8. Seattle, WA. 1936 May.
      - What is Democracy Worth to You- All-Out-Aid to Finance All-Out-Defense Services. Pamphlet. Greater Seattle Defense Chest Campaign. 1941.
      - "A Prospectus of State Road No. 19." Wahkiakum County Development League. Cathlamet, WA. Circa 1919.
      - "Martin for Governor" signs.
      - Now! About the Election Business. Booklet for Al Canwell for Congress. Circa 1940.
      - "Read Why (in 5 Minutes) Frank T. Bell Should be Elected Congressman, Fourth District, Washington, Democratic Ticket." Pamphlet. Circa 1940s.
      - "For Governor." George H. Gannon pamphlet. Gannon-for-Governor committee. 1940.
      - Leaflet for Al McCoy, democratic candidate for Congress. Circa 1940s.
      - Leaflet for meeting on repealing 18th Amendment, held by Laurence Colman, candidate for Delegate to the State Convention. Circa 1930s.
      - Lift Washington with Gannon. Election literature. Pullman Gannon-for-Governor Club. Circa 1940.
      - "Let's Check the Record: Accomplishments of Governor Albert D. Rosellini, Democrat." Flipbook. Washington State Democratic Committee. Circa 1960s.
      - Cheney
        - "Vote for Clarence D. Martin, Democratic Candidate for Representative, Fourth Legislative District, Cheney" placards.
      - Pullman
        - "Ordinance No. 345." City of Pullman. 1917.
        - "Why Not Make Pullman a Better Place to Live?" Brochure. 1970.
        - New Choices in City Government: An Examination of the Optional Municipal Code with References to Pullman. League of Women Voters, Pullman, WA, pamphlet. 1970 January.
        - Palouse Patriot. Newsletters. 2009. (3 items)
        - "Pullman-Moscow Tea Party." Broadside. 2010.
        - Karen Kiessling for Mayor campaign leaflets. 1975.
        - "Know Your Government." Old National Bank. Pullman, WA. 1975 and 1976. (2 items)
        - "Report from Your Mayor." City of Pullman, Washington. Report for 1962.
      - Seattle
        - The New Charter of the City of Seattle. 1946.
      - Spokane
        - Constitutional Government League constitution and officer list. Brochure. Circa 1919.
        - "Voters Guide--Spokane City Election--Primary--February 25, Run-off--March 11, 1947." Committee of 1000.
        - Water rate schedule. City of Spokane. 1928.
        - "Proposed Bond Issue for Trunk Line Road System." Spokane County, WA. Board of County Commissioners. (2 copies)
      - Whitman County
        - "Whitman County Republican Club" cards
        - "W. O. 'Bill' Druffel, Republican Candidate for County Commissioner" card.
  - Unsorted Items
- Products (consumer) -- Advertising, catalogs, manuals, etc.
  - Appliances
    - "How to Choose And Use Your Refrigerator." Pamphlet. U.S. Department of Agriculture. 1946.
    - Household Equipment: its care and simple repair. Pamphlet. Agricultural Extension Service, State College of Washington. Ext. Bulletin 301. Pullman, WA. December, 1943.
    - Recommended Practice of Home Lighting. Illuminating Engineering Society. June, 1945.
    - Light for Living...Today and Tomorrow. Lamp Department of General Electric Company. 1945.
    - A Reference Manual on Electric Home Appliances. Reference Handbook No. 1. Westinghouse Educational Series. 1946 Edition.
    - "The Lowest Priced Quality Washer." Homer King, Inc. Tacoma, WA. Circa 1920s-1930s.
    - "Kitch-n Handy Cabinet Hardware and Kitchen Accessories." Folder. Washington Steel Products Co. Seattle, WA. (Location note: in Oversize 1)
    - "The Delco-Heat Im-Pak-Tor Boiler." Booklet. General Motors. Circa 1920s.
    - "The Delco-Heat Conditioner." Booklet. General Motors. Circa 1920s.
    - "The Delco-Heat Burner with the 'Thin Mix' Fuel Control." General Motors. Circa 1920s.
    - "Air Conditioning." Booklet. Frigidaire Corporation. Dayton, Ohio. 1935.
    - "Luxurious Heat." Booklet. General Electric. Circa 1930s.
    - The Man Who Revolutionized the American Home. Lowell Thomas. Booklet. Scott 7 Fitzer Company. Cleveland, OH. 1936.
    - "This New Comfort." Booklet. American Radiator Company. New York. Circa 1930s.
    - "Presenting Hoffman Controlled Heat with Air-Conditioning." Booklet. Hoffman Specialty Co., Inc. Waterbury, CT. Circa 1925.
  - Other
    - "Semi-Hex Pencils." Blotter. Pullman, WA.
    - Reproduction (broadside) of advertisement page from The New York Times, 1948 April 9, concerning Edward R. Murrow. (Location note: in Oversize 1)
    - Sales flyer for the Kansas City Novelty Co. featuring "sensational books" (sexual content). Circa 1900-1910.
    - 1924-1925 Price List of United States Stamps and Supplies. Booklet. Sold by B.L. Voorhees. Chicago, Il.
    - Steuben Glass Catalog. J.B. Hudson, Co. Minneapolis. 1955.
    - Steuben Glass Catalog, J.B. Hudson, Co. Minneapolis. 1954.
    - Sears, Roebuck & Co. sales literature. Envelope containing ads for cream separator, buggy, paint, and washing machine. Circa 1900.
    - Interesting Bedrooms in the Homes of Well-Known Women. Magazine. C.E. Suffield. Dayton, WA. Circa 1920s.
    - Fashions of the Hour. Magazine. Frederick Nelson. Christmas, 1950.
  - Unsorted Items
- Religion, Churches
  - The Society of Friends. Jane P. Rushmore. Pamphlet.
  - Recruiting the Priesthood. Report of Seminary Collection. 1934.
  - A Quaker Meeting for Worship. Douglas V. Steere. Philadelphia. 1949.
  - Quaker Testimonies in daily life. Frederick B. Tolles. Philadelphia.
  - Americans All: A Short History of American Jews. Chicago: Anti-Defamation League. Circa 1942-1945.
  - "Evening Service." Program for United Presbyterian Church. 1908.
  - American Missionary Association Life Membership certificate. 1854. (Location note: oversize 2).
  - Tracts, sermons, miscellaneous
    - Popular Amusements and The Christian Life. Rev. Perry Wayland Sinks. 1896.
    - "In the Beginning God--" And Other Talks. Mark A. Matthews. 1924.
    - The Mass Versus The Lord's Supper. H. A. Ironside. 1926.
    - The Second Coming of Christ. Moody, Ryle, Harriet Beecher Stowe. 1896.
    - Heaven: Its Hope, Its Inhabitants, Its Happiness, Its Certainty, Its Richness, Its Rewards. D. L. Moody. 1908.
  - Pullman, WA
    - Baptist Broadcaster. Pullman, WA. 1926 January.
    - The Baptist Broadcaster. Pullman, WA. 1926 February.
    - "Souvenir of the Dedication of Services of St. Patrick's Church. Program. Colfax, WA. 1895 March 17. (Location note: Oversize 2)
- Sports
  - George Musso souvenir football card, signed.
  - Pullman (WA) High School football program.
  - "All-American Football Game." Folded cardboard football game. Zenith Radio Tubes. 1938.
  - Rolling Hills Roller Derby. Pamphlet. Pullman, WA. Circa 2010s.
  - "Malice in Wonderland." Roller Derby program. Pullman, WA. Circa 2010s.
  - "Malice in Wonderland." Poster advertisement. Pullman, WA. Circa 2010s. (Location note: oversize 2)
  - "Shamrock Shakedown." Roller Derby program. Pullman, WA. Circa 2010s.
  - Oregon vs. Washington State football ticket stub. November 11, 1961.
- Taxidermy
  - "Illustrated Catalogue of Taxidermists, Naturalists and Oölogists Instruments." Codman and Shurtleff. Boston, Mass.
- Theater
  - Performance programs
    - "In the Snare." The Magazine-Programme.
    - "Yoicks!" Kingsway Theatre. The Magazine-Programme, No. 519.
    - "The Wandering Jew." Programme. New Theatre.
    - "The Tyrant." Programme. New Theatre, London.
    - "Fata Morgana." Programme. Criterion Theatre.
    - "Souvenir Programme: Rudolph Valentino in 'Monsieur Beaucaire' at the London Pavilion." The Magazine-Programme.
    - "Theatrical Garden Party." Actor's Orphanage, Royal Hospital, Gardens Chelsea. 1925 June 30.
    - "The Pelican." Ambassadors Theatre. The Magazine-Programme, No. 505.
    - "The Rat." Prince of Wales' Theatre. The Magazine-Programme.
    - "Treasure Island." Strand Theatre, London. The Magazine-Programme, No. 514.
    - "The Fool." Programme. Apollo Theatre, London.
    - "The Co-Optimists." The Palace [Theatre], London. The Magazine-Programme, No. 523.
    - "By the Way." Programme. Apollo Theatre, London.
    - "The Mask and the Face." Criterion Theatre.
    - "Betty in Mayfair." Adelphi Theatre.
    - "The Chinese Bungalow." The Magazine-Programme, No. 578. The Golders Green Hippodrome, London.
    - "The Madras House." The Magazine-Programme, No. 565. Ambassadors Theatre, London.
    - "The Farmer's Wife." The Magazine-Programme, No. 539. Royal Court Theatre, London.
    - "R.S.V.P." Programme. Vaudeville Theatre, London.
    - "The Honourable Mr. Tawnish." Programme. King's Theatre, London.
    - "Good Luck." Programme. Theatre Royal, London.
    - "The Hour and the Man." Programme. New Theatre, London.
    - "Operette." Programme. His Majesty's Theatre, London.
    - "The Sport of Kings." The Magazine-Programme, No. 524. Savoy Theatre, London.
    - "The Vortex." The Magazine-Programme, No. 527. Comedy Theatre, London.
    - "Cobra." The Magazine-Programme, No. 548. Garrick Theatre, London.
    - "White Cargo." Programme. The Playhouse, London.
    - "The D'Oyly Carte Opera Company." The Magazine-Programme, No. 553. The Golders Green Hippodrome, London.
    - "The Last of Mrs. Cheyney." The Magazine-Programme, No. 571. The Golders Green Hippodrome, London.
    - "The Scarlet Pimpernel." Programme Cover. Brixton Theatre, London.
    - "The Honourable Mr. Tawnish." Advertisement. King's Theatre, London.
    - "The Apache." Programme. The Palladium, London. 2 copies.
    - "Ben-Hur." Programme. The Tivoli Strand.
    - "The Man in Dress Clothes." Programme. Lyceum Theatre Strand.
    - "Dancing Mothers." Programme. Queen's Theatre, London.
    - "The Odd Spot." Programme. Little Theatre, London.
    - "Alf's Button." Programme. Princess Theatre, London.
    - "The Blue Peter." Programme. Princess Theatre.
    - "The Royal Carl Rosa Opera Company." Programme. Lyceum Theatre Strand.